{
    "id": "c013ad89a392462c80ba04e96958170d",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The meeting has been ………………………….",
            "description": "To put off is to postpone.",
            "answers": [
                "put up",
                "put out",
                "put off"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Julie ………………………… us yesterday.",
            "description": "To call on is to visit.",
            "answers": [
                "called at",
                "called up",
                "called on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It took me quite some time to …………………………. her demise.",
            "description": "To get over is to overcome. ",
            "answers": [
                "get out",
                "get on",
                "get over"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Although we had little chance of success, we didn’t ………………………… hope.",
            "description": "To give up is to stop.",
            "answers": [
                "give in",
                "give off",
                "give up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t ………………………… with her in laws.",
            "description": "To get along is to have friendly relationship.",
            "answers": [
                "get along",
                "get in",
                "get off"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………….. when he was just",
            "description": "To pass away is to die. ",
            "answers": [
                "passed out",
                "passed off",
                "passed away"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "After having put a lot of effort …………………….. this project, I don’t want it to fail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If that table ………………………… a lot of space, it should be moved to the hall.",
            "description": "To take up space is to occupy it.",
            "answers": [
                "takes on",
                "takes off",
                "takes up"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher advised the students to ………………………… their lessons before the exam.",
            "description": "To go through the lessons is to revise the lessons.",
            "answers": [
                "go over",
                "go through",
                "go on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Firemen were called in to ……………………………. the fire.",
            "description": "To put out is to extinguish.",
            "answers": [
                "put off",
                "put up",
                "put out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They are …………………… a new edition of that book.",
            "description": "To bring out a book is to publish it.",
            "answers": [
                "bringing out",
                "bringing up",
                "bringing on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "While cleaning the attic, I ………………………. these old photos of mine.",
            "description": "To come across is to find by chance. ",
            "answers": [
                "came off",
                "came through",
                "came across"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}